Guide to the Records of the Institute of African American Affairs RG.9.8
New York University Archives
- Series V: Administrative Files
  - Black Cinema, 1994
  - Black Thought in Progress Lecture Series - Patricia Hill Collins, 1995
  - African Art Symposium, 1995
  - Promotional Materials, 1995-1997
  - Black Thought, 1996-1996
  - Angela Davis (Press), 1993-1994
  - Clippings, 1996-1997
  - Promotional Materials, 1998
  - Promotional Materials, 1999-2000
  - Promotional Materials, 2002
- Unprocessed Records (Box 38, Box 42, Box 43, Box 44, Box 45, Box 46, Box 47, Box 48, Box 112)